# Shehroz Reza

## **Software Engineer**

Motihari, Bihar shehrozr@gmail.com 07696286887

Worked on Java Card sim appket tester and developer. As a tester used to prepare and format data for the testing using python script while development of application was done in Java Card

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

## Work Experience

### **Software Engineer**

Idemia

January 2018 to September 2018

Worked on Java Card sim applet tester and developer. As a tester used to prepare and format data for the testing using python script while development of application was done in Java Card

### **Associate Software Engineer**

Vihaan (OT Morpho) July 2017 to December 2017

#### Intern

Solitaire Infosys January 2017 to May 2017

Worked as an intern on a Home Automation project based on embedded systems.

### Education

#### **Master of Science in Data Science**

Royal Holloway University of London - Egham 2018 to 2019

## **Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science**

CGC College of Engineering (Punjab Technical University) 2013 to 2017

## Skills / IT Skills

PYTHON (4 years), REQUIREMENT ANALYSIS (2 years), MACHINE LEARNING (1 year), NATURAL LANGUAGE PROCESSING (Less than 1 year), R (Less than 1 year), AWS (Less than 1 year), Java Card (1 year)

# Online Profile

## http://linkedin.com/in/shehrozreza010

# Additional Information

## SKILLS

- Python R
- Machine Learning Spark
- Deep Learning Java Card
- SQL Visualization
- Requirement Analysis Natural Language Processing
- Conformal & Non-Conformal Prediction